click.org 2019-01-05

# Privacy Policy

OUR ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY

Click.org has established this Privacy Policy to explain how it protects and manages the personal information that it collects from you (the customer) online. 

1.Consent for Collection, Use and Disclosure

Your use of the Click.org site and/or your registration for Click.org products and services constitute your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Click.org site. 

Click.org may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When it does, Click.org will also revise the "last update" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. In addition, Click.org will seek a customer�s prior consent, by email, for any new uses or proposed disclosures of information collected from the customer prior to the change. Click.org will notify customers by email of changes to this policy that will affect information collected from them in the future. In certain circumstances, however, Click.org will not inform and obtain the consent of the customer, such as in connection with an investigation of a breach of an agreement, contravention of laws, an emergency where the life, health or security of an individual is threatened, the collection of a debt or in compliance with the request of a law enforcement agency or a court order.

A customer may withdraw his or her consent for collection, use and disclosure at any time by contacting us 

. Please note that if you do, Click.org may suspend its provision of products and services to you. 

2\. Accountability

Click.org collects, at the time of your registration and your sign-on to its web site, certain "personal information" (information that personally identifies you) including but not limited to your name, email address, home or work address, telephone number etc. and information about your computer hardware and software (e.g., IP address, operating system, browser type, domain name, URL, access times, and referring web site addresses). 

Click.org has implemented this Privacy Policy to protect personal information received from its customers, and to respond to any inquiries. The Privacy Policy also provides that Click.org will use appropriate contractual means to establish a comparable level of protection for personal information which is sent for processing by third parties on Click.org behalf. 

3\. Purposes for Collecting Personal Information

Click.org collects and uses personal information for the following purposes:

(a) to understand customer needs regarding Click.org services;

(b) to develop and provide our web site and our products and services for our customers;

(c) to fulfill your requests for products, services or information; 

(d) to communicate with customers and site visitors, when necessary, and to inform customers of upgrades, as well as of other products and services available from Click.org, its affiliates and third parties;

(e) to allow customers to access limited-entry areas of Click.org site;

(f) to personalize some of our services and products for you and to deliver targeted advertisements and offers from Click.org and third parties;

(g) to bill accounts and maintain payment records; 

(h) to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or government request;

(i) to respond to a legitimate claim, or to address our reasonable belief, that you are violating the rights of any third party or any of the agreements or policies that govern your use of the Click.org site or any Click.org product or service;

(j) to protect the services, products or rights of Click.org, including but not limited to the security or integrity of the Click.org site; and

(k) to identify and resolve technical problems concerning Click.org site, products and services. 

Click.org also uses personal information in an aggregate form (i.e., not individually attributable to you) for its business analysis, operational, marketing and other promotional purposes. If we hire other companies to provide some products or services on our behalf, then we will only provide those companies the personal information they need for the Identified Purposes, and we will limit their rights to use and further disclose your personal information as appropriate in the course of their work for us.

4\. Limiting the Collection of Personal Information

Click.org limits its collection of personal information to only that information which is necessary for the Identified Purposes. Click.org does not direct its site to, nor does it knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen.

When you visit the Click.org web site, a cookie may be placed on your computer or the cookie may be read if you have visited the Click.org site previously. Click.org uses cookies to allow Click.org to determine which products and services you have already purchased so that Click.org does not provide redundant information to you, and, if you are an Click.org affiliate, to track Click.org sales made to customers referred by you so that you can receive compensation under our affiliate program. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the Click.org web site, you may not be able to view all the text on the screens, or to experience a personalized visit, or to subscribe to certain service and product offerings on the Click.org site.

5\. Disclosure, Processing and Retention 

From time to time, Click.org may disclose certain personally identifiable information with affiliated business partners or authorized third parties on a need to know basis for evaluating authorized customers for service eligibility. With exception to the above, Click.org does not sell, rent or disclose your personal information to anyone else, except:

(a) to someone you have designated to act as your agent, for one or more of the Identified Purposes (listed in Section 2, above);

(b) to Click.org employees, independent contractors, subsidiaries, affiliates, consultants, business associates, service providers, suppliers and agents, acting on Click.org behalf for any of the Identified Purposes;

(c) as necessary if Click.org has reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with Click.org rights or property, other users of Click.org web site, products or services, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities; and

(d) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law. 

In addition, as we continue to develop our business, we may sell or buy other businesses or entities, or we may merge with another company. In such transactions, personal information may be one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that Click.org or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets.

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States, or in any other country in which Click.org or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities. By using this web site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

After your account becomes inactive (that is, if you request to be removed from our database), Click.org will keep your personal information in its archives. Your information will then be used only as necessary for tax reasons or to prove Click.org compliance with any applicable law. 

6\. Accuracy of Personal Information

Click.org will use reasonable efforts to keep customer personal information accurate for the Identified Purposes, and for minimizing the possibility of making inappropriate customer decisions based on such information. Customers are responsible for informing Click.org about changes to their personal information. You can do this by [contacting us](http://click.org/contact-us.htm). Click.org will use new or updated personal information it receives from customers to update its own records. 

7\. Security Safeguards

Click.org will use reasonable efforts to protect customers� personal information.

8\. Access to Personal Information

Click.org will afford you a reasonable opportunity to review the personal information in your file, if you so request by faxing 480-393-5100.

If Click.org is not able to provide access to some aspect of a customer�s personal information, it will provide reasons for denying access such as; that by doing so would likely reveal personal information about a third party, or that it is confidential commercial information or attorney�client privileged communications, or that the information relates to a breach of an agreement or a contravention of law, or that its disclosure could reasonably be expected to threaten the life or security of another individual.

Customers have the right to request that inaccurate or incomplete information be amended as appropriate, by contacting Click.org or as described above. Click.org will promptly correct such personal information.
